So every day I wake up and the first thing I do is I go through the Internet to see what is going on in the world today.
And every day there is something that makes me look like I'm not even together yet.
That makes me compelled to have to like speak.
And I'm wondering why I do not see more of my peers doing the same.
It's not like y'all aren't on this app.
Or other apps.
And maybe they're donating money.
You know what I'm saying?
Like maybe they're more so on the covert element of it.
But we need to acknowledge the value of volume, of amplification, and of the representation of seeing the people that are in your homes, in TV, that are in your lives in film, that are in your ears in podcasts, etc.
That are on your phones influencing.
Seeing those people also in your space, speaking to the things that are happening to affect our world.
So I'm calling on all my peers to make a decision to make a shift.
You have platforms and you have fans and supporters who love you.
And with our exposure, we're not here to just play roles on screen.
We have a role to play in using our platforms for change.
Let's talk to ourselves.
Thank you.
Have a great day.
Take care.
Bye.